(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-26T23:23:19.156888",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
注意事項
[Attention For Visitors]
コンサートグッズ第2次販売
[2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales]
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
注意事項
[Attention For Visitors]
コンサートグッズ第2次販売
[2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales]
Greetings, CC, my fated rival.
Greetings, Ina, my destined rival!
And hello to everyone watching from...
Serendipity!
Woo!
Remember, if you want a chance for your wish to be featured on the Otomo or the Takodachi that we made...
post about it with #WishUponTakoTomo!
Yay!
Thank you, Amiami, for supporting our rivalry!
And for supporting Serendipity!
Be sure to check out their booth at...
Anime Expo!
Yeah!
Hey pebbles!
It's Koseki Bijou!
Bi-boo!
And all of hololive BASE is here with me, all 14 of us!
hololive BASE is coming to Round1 USA locations nationwide...
...starting this September.
Come hang out with us!
Follow @round1usa on Instagram and X so you don't miss out on any updates!
We can't wait to see you there! Bye-bye!
[On-Screen: The concert will be starting soon.]
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Acrylic Stand
Button Badge / Acrylic Panel
hololive English 4th Concert - Serendipity
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors: Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Attention For Visitors: Cheering loudly is ok.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Acrylic Stand
Button Badge / Acrylic Panel
hololive English 4th Concert - Serendipity
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
ご来場の皆様へ：公演中のフラッシュライトにご注意ください。
Attention Visitors: Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
大声での声援は可能です。
Cheering loudly is ok.
コンサートグッズ第2次販売
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
アクリルスタンド / アクリルパネル
Acrylic Stand & Acrylic Panel
缶バッジ / ステッカー
Button Badge & Stickers
The concert will be starting soon. 開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a moment for the performance to begin.
Attention For Visitors: Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is OK.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Let's sing our bold words again
Continuing this fantasy, we'll start this new refrain
Brimming with memories
And when the cloudy skies become bright
Let's reunite!
What's up everyone! Welcome to hololive English 4th Concert: SerendipiTy!
Whoa, and we're back!
Let's kick off the show with a Myth medley!
Ready? 1, 2, 3!
Showtime baby, I would say
Today's performance has a slight delay
Waving off the scuff, is it really enough
To keep us buffering endlessly? Why?!
Take it easy, what did we learn?
Set a fire in the hearth and the PC burns down
Optimistic, focus on a quick fix
Teach new dogs all of our old tricks
Becoming stronger than ever and never saying die
And I'm aware it's ironic, but where's the freaking line?
Dreamers to dreamers, entertainers to simps
Am I losing you, young people?
Ignore her, it's a Myth, let's practice! Here we go!
Spanning new dimensions
We can bring another mystery to light
Blending our ascension, dancing in stride, we ignite
Join us while we're celebrating
In the myth that we're creating
There's another story waiting
Through this world and beyond!
Our distant dreams have brought us here
A strong, unyielding bond, guiding us endlessly
That brings us moments that we hold dear
Time rushes on
And though these winds may scatter us
We'll keep this promise
When the moment's finally right
We'll always find a way to reunite!
1, 2, 3!
Light, light, light, light, light, let's begin
We'll start today right and shuffle on in
We are ready to steal the show
We're jumping with joy, let's go!
Cartoons are so cute, the band will keep on entertaining
Hand in hand!
It's our greatest moment yet
A spectacle we'll never forget
We're gonna party from dusk till dawn, the show, yeah, it'll go on and on
Proud of that we're here to stay
And spread the news from Tokyo to Broadway!
Gleaming in the spotlight, get-together
We'll be boogying all night
Beaming so bright
Now we're feeling alright!
Since the day we met, we've fallen and grown strong
And we'll keep moving right along
So we'll keep on dancing on our feet
And nothing can stop our perfect quintet
In harmony, no matter where we go
Like we're meant to be, don't you know?
We're gonna feel so alive when it all spins
Ready to put on another show!
There's an answer out there somewhere
When the muses whisper truth or dare
A hazard for a blood-soaked war
But no one's keeping score
Stay course and be tenacious
'Cause the future is a game of chance
The chips are down, we're all in
I'll play until I win
I'm not gonna give up now
The wheels of fortune circle back around
A turn in the betting ring
A lethal outcome strongly governing
And through this tangled thread
I see what's up ahead
A line chase
A straight face
I got to try my luck, I'll spin the thread
Spin the roulette, see where it falls
Testing the limits and betting it all
Round and round, jumping into the circle
Over and over, we test our world
Oh, the game is never easy
And the outcome is a mystery
But these are fates we're betting on
Our threads unbroken
Called to life by flaxen string
Crossing paths together
At the start of everything
I'm not gonna give up yet
I spin back round with every chance I get
The wheel turns in a dire grasp
The time has come for fate to change at last
And with this flicker of red
I'm moving up ahead
A golden chance
A daring dance
I spin this wheel of fate with my own hands
I'm taking fate into my hands
Whoa, yeah
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead
Blazin' fire!
Can't control it anymore, I'm burnin' up red
Crazy thoughts fillin' my head
(Tension rising to the top)
(Won't look back, I'll never stop)
(Blazing, boiling, gettin' hot)
(It's your fault, baby)
Fever burning up inside
It can't be contained
Got my heart goin' up in flames
Tell me you can feel
The searing heat
(Come on and come on, I wanna confess)
(Baby, oh baby, I'm gettin' obsessed)
Are you gonna run away
Or burn up with me?
(Crank it up, crank it up, hotter and hotter)
(Gonna be, wanna be ready for more)
I'm caught in a heat wave, I'll never get enough
Fanning the flame of love
(And now it's taking over)
Blazin' fire, make me a believer
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burnin' like a fever
Come hold me close if you dare!
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Sweet love, burn me away
Blazin' fire!
(I'm gonna wanna turn it up, I'm burnin' up, can't get enough)
(Maybe I'm too hot to touch)
(It's your fault, baby)
I can't hide it anymore, I'm bearing my soul
Let these flames swallow me whole
This is how we're gonna play; a dangerous game
Got your fire runnin' through my veins
Baby, can't you read between the lines?
(Look at me, look at me, turnin' to ash)
(Breakin' me, shakin' me, makin' me crash)
Gonna sear it all away until you're mine
(Drivin' me, drivin' me, drivin' me crazy)
(Tellin' me, tellin' me what do you mean)
I'm caught in a heat wave, I'll never get enough
Fanning the flame of love
(And now it's taking over)
Blazin' fire, make me a believer
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burnin' like a fever
Come hold me close if you dare!
Fire lover, be my flame
Come hold me close if you dare
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Sweet love, burn me away
Blazing fire, show me your illusion
It doesn't matter if it's real or a dream
Wild desire, fueling my delusion
I want you burning for me
Blazing fire, make me a believer
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burnin' like a fever
Come hold me close if you dare
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Sweet love, burn me away
Gigi Murin
Cecilia Immergreen
AutoFister
Otomos, now listen...
CCGG madness!
Grems, get in position!
Orange green division
AutoFister!
Hey, hey! CCGG mad fun!
Hey, hey! Gremlin automaton!
Guten Tag! Can you tell me where the bathroom is?
I've been walking around all day and I really need to go...
Uh... no.
But I've seen this new super cute cafe around the corner,
and they sell tea and Baumkuchen!
Sorry, I don't speak German.
Oh...
On this day, you are cursed to cope
And keep it in your memory
Oh, come on, you're supposed to hope
And let our brand of madness run its course!
Take our hand, let's fly away!
Break a leg now, challenge fate!
Quick before your time's up,
Give in and be our playmate!
Hop, step, jump, our dreams await!
Love yourself, don't be afraid!
Sign just one condition:
Give in, release all inhibition!
CCGG, CCGG, CCGG madness!
Oh, CCGG, CCGG, AutoFister!
Oh, CCGG, CCGG, come let's play!
Come on, LA! We want to hear you shout!
Recently, mmm... I've just been having so much anxiety...
Cause I can't find a single manga that I like-like.
Yeah?
I like so many different genres like romance, romance, and romance!
But I just don't know what to do!
Sorry, what did you say? I was looking at my phone.
Ugh!
Oh, come on, can a girl not hope
To lose your heart in reverie?
There's no way to divert this trope,
So let our brand of madness run its course!
Take our hand, let's fly away!
Make a way now, choose a date!
Quick before your time's up,
Give in and be our playmate!
Hop, step, jump, our dreams await!
Love yourself, don't be afraid!
Live up your ambition,
Come on, let go of intuition!
CCGG, CCGG, CCGG madness!
Oh, CCGG, CCGG, AutoFister!
Oh, CCGG, CCGG, come and play!
Look at the people, Gigi! Look at them!
I see them! They're so big!
Look at the glowsticks!
There's green and orange!
And they're waving them!
Oh my god, look at that one!
Where? Right there?
Yeah! Everyone, thank you so much!
All our fun must come to an end
But at least you've found a friend
So let us play and stay forever
...or rather
One, two, yeah!
Take our hand and let's fly away
Turn around and let us play
Find just one good reason, come on
Join in our safe adventure!
Fly away...
La, la, la, la...
Come let's play!
Hello, hello, hello!
Hello!
Welcome to Justice's very first, and chat's greatest tweet:
"My butt's too big for this seat!" Ahhh!
Wow, look at it, it's so big and juicy, how impressive! Hello everyone!
It's me, Cecilia Immergreen!
And me, Gigi Murin!
And together we are...
Auto-fister!
Well LA, we wanted to do some LA call and response!
So I'm going to say something, and you cheer if you like it, okay?
Okay?
The beach!
Hololive in LA!
Sitting in traffic!
Booo... Whatever.
CCGG in LA!
Okay, we're very, very excited to be here at Hololive Summer...
Summer Skibidi!
Summer Skibidi...
Please all stand, it is the 4th of July weekend... for the flag...
Please stand up, everyone!
Oh say, can you see...
By the dawn's early light... what so proudly...
Okay, okay, okay, shut up, shut up, shut up, that's enough, enough, enough.
Enough of that. Enough of that chit... Okay.
How about we do a CCGG chant?
How do we do...
No, no, no, no, not yet, not yet, not yet, not yet!
USA, janai. No, no, no, no.
Not USA. No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay guys, since you are standing, we want you to do our chant of our chorus, plus...
Stomping!
Stomping to the beat, okay?
So, the left side, we want them to be green...
And this side...
Green! Orange!
Green! Orange! Do it now!
Quickly!
Okay, perfect, perfect, perfect!
Good, okay, okay, okay.
Stomping, and then we say, "CCGG CCGG."
Yes, yes.
CC! GG! CC! GG!
CC! GG! Madness!
CC! GG! CC! GG! CC! GG! Auto-fister!
CC! GG! CC! GG! CC! GG! Madness!
CC! GG! CC! GG! Come let's play!
Okay, issho ni!
Okay, together!
Everyone together really fast though.
Show, impress us, okay?
Okay.
Are you ready? Are you ready? Okay.
CCGG CCGG CCGG Madness!
CCGG CCGG CCGG Auto-fister!
CCGG CCGG CCGG Come let's play!
Really impressive, guys, that was really, really good.
Maybe America is awesome.
USA! USA! USA!
Yeah, they freaking love us again.
In America... In America.
Well, for those at home...
This is sadly the end of the free section.
There's one more song, actually, a song after this.
Oh, one more song? Sorry, sorry, sorry.
But there's the tickets for the streaming tickets down below, so please check them out!
In the description, check out the streaming tickets, okay?
Auto-fister's forgot to do this today, okay?
And...
無料配信は次の曲で最後になります！ライブの続きはぜひ配信チケットを買ってみてね！
The free stream will end with the next song! Please buy the stream tickets to watch the rest of the live concert!
買ってみてね！
Please buy them!
Or we'll hate... all you freaking haters, okay?
Don't hate us, don't be a freaking loser.
Don't hate us. For the very last part...
Since this is the very first MC, we want you to be as loud as possible, okay?
So...
Thank you, thank you, thank you! Thank you!
We will become a bowling ball and a bowling pin,
and we need you to chant "Serendipity", right? Okay?
Keep chanting until we're gone, okay?
Keep chanting until we're gone!
Don't stop until we're gone!
Don't stop!
Okay.
Well, one time together, everyone!
Serendipity!
I'll be your executioner, the one on the gavel
Sentenced me to doom, even though I'm still ruling what you do
Decide which lies become the truth
No, you never really thought about it that far
Judging me when I can see you've got the same scars
That's the price that I paid, so steal these marks
Come pick your sacrifice
Nail me to your crucifix
Nothing else can fix this
So I'll take the blame
See yourself reflected
And not corrected
One requested
Don't be gentle
Don't be kind when you're
When you're...
Hold their eyes out, leave them blind
One requested
Pharisee, I've seen what you're doing in private things
All your friends, yeah, they know what you're really thinking
To your glory, the masses keep on singing
Point at me in a hurry, need a scapegoat for the new controversy
Even when I'm buried, hidden in silence, you'll be wary
Priest or God, show no mercy
Nail me to your crucifix
Nothing else can fix this
So I'll take the blame
See yourself reflected
And not corrected
One requested
Don't be gentle
Don't be kind when you're
When you're...
Hold their eyes out, leave them blind
Raise me now
Take me down
Leave me now
One requested
I see your sins and they're in your soul consuming
Ignored decay to your core
I'll never win to you but within
Break, break, break...
you win...
And in your hands the hammer pounds
Constant, and I'm still counting
Don't be gentle
Don't be kind when you're
Murder, murder, murder
Hold their eyes out, leave them blind
One requested
One requested...
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！